REAL WEBRTC · HYPERREAL CONVERSATIONAL V3
SIX-POSE IDLE SHOWCASE
NEUTRAL RESTING
faint breathing · brief blinks · no head wandering
ACTIVE LISTENING
one shallow acknowledgement · attentive eyes
SPEAKING DIRECT · IDLE PREVIEW
small conversational emphasis · planted shoulders
NOD / AGREEMENT
one compact nod · no repetition
EMPATHETIC HEAD TILT
subtle held inclination · softened expression
LIGHT SMILE
restrained closed-lip smile · stable posture
NEUTRAL RESTING
quiet baseline before the live response
LIVE TTS + MUSETALK LIP SYNC
LIGHT-SMILE REACTION
restrained reaction with live MuseTalk lip sync
SPEAKING DIRECT
calm conversational delivery with live lip sync
NEUTRAL RETURN
quiet settling through speech completion